hasnihon.com 2011-11-04

# Japanese Used Car|Damaged Car|Passenger Car|Sedan Car|Sports Car|Used Car Auction

This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors and registered members who are using this web site even for visiting or searching or ordering Japanese used vehicles or Parts from Japan or our other services. You accepted this policy when you signed up for our Service. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our web site. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. In addition, if the revised version includes a substantial change, we will provide you with 30 days’ prior notice by posting notice of the change on the "Policy Updates" page of our web site. We last modified this Policy on February 25, 2008

 **How we collect information about you**

When you visit the Has-Nihon web sites, we collect your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our web site.

If you open an account, we collect the following types of information from you:   
1- Contact information - your name, address, phone, email, Skype ID and other similar information.   
2- Financial information - the bank account numbers and credit card numbers that you link to your Has-Nihon account. 

Before permitting you to use our Service, we may require you to provide additional information we can use to verify your identity or address or manage risk, such as your date of birth, ID copy, ID Number or other information. We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as credit bureaus and identity verification services.

When you are using our Service, we collect information about your account transactions and we may collect information about your computer or other access device for fraud prevention purposes.

Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey.

 **How we use cookies**

When you access our web site, we, or companies we hire to track how our web site is used, may place small data files called "cookies" on your computer. 

We send a "session cookie" to your computer when you log in to your account. This type of cookie helps us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session, so that we don’t need to ask you for your password on each page. Once you log out or close your browser, this cookie expires and no longer has any effect.You may choose remember me which leads the cookie remaining on your computer for specific period of time.

We also use longer-lasting cookies to display your e-mail address on our sign-in form, so that you don't need to retype the e-mail address each time you log in to your account. 

We encode our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our web site. 

**How we protect and store personal information**

Throughout this policy, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not identify a specific user. 

**How we use the personal information we collect**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We may use your personal information to: 

provide the services and customer support you request; 

process transactions and send notices about your transactions 

resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 

prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement; 

customize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our web site; 

send you targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; 

compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties.

 **How we share personal information with other parties**

We may share your personal information with: 

Members of our corporate family (these are companies owned by our company such as www.Auctiondatasearch.jp or ...) to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts, provide joint services and for other business purposes. However, these corporate affiliates will not use this information to market their services to you unless you have approved it. 

Service providers under contract who help with parts of our business operations; (fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, technology services). Our contracts dictate that these service providers only use your information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for their own benefit. 

Financial institutions that we partner with to jointly create and offer a product such as the PayPal Plus credit card where we share information with our merchant Bank to determine whether you should receive pre-approved offers for the PayPal Plus credit card. These financial institutions may only use this information to market PayPal-related or Credit Card related Bank, unless you have given consent for other uses. 

Credit bureaus to report outstanding negative balance accounts, as allowed by law. 

Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when 

> 1- we are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure 
> 
> 2- we need to do so to comply with law 
> 
> 3- we believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our User Agreement. 

Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so. 

> **Has-Nihon will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties in the normal course of doing business and only shares your personal information with third parties as described in this policy.**

 **How you can contact us about privacy questions**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact us by this E-mail address: ext_legal [at] hasnihon [dot] com (use @ mark instead of [at] and . mark instead of [dot]). or writing to us at Has-Nihon Trading CO.,LTD. 1158-1 NAKA-SHINDEN, SAYAMA CITY, SAITAMA PREFECTURE, JAPAN 350-1311
